( birds chirping )
( wind blowing , birds chirping )
( children chattering )
HANNIBAL : Hide quickly !
Run away !
( animals calling , rustling )
( water rippling )
( snorting )
HANNIBAL : Quick ! This way !
Quickly !
HANNIBAL : Down to the lake .
( giggling )
Oh-eeh ...
- M ... for Mischa . - Mischa .
- ( explosion ) - ( both gasp )
( birds calling )
HANNIBAL : Come on ! Come on , let 's go !
( airplane roars )
( horse whinnies )
Come on , Lothar .
- Hurry now . Give me the bathtub . - Yes , sir .
( grunts )
FATHER LECTER : Hannibal , Mischa , where have you been ?
- Hurry now ! Quickly ! - ( explosion )
( Hannibal grunts )
MOTHER LECTER : Hannibal !
Come here .
Come on !
FATHER LECTER : Darling ...
The cart is packed . Everything is ready .
( explosions )
Hurry up . Come on , come on .
BERNDT : Come along . Come on .
( horse whinnies )
Hey .
Colonel Timka says the fighting will be close to the roads .
Can 't last more than a few days .
We 'll be safe at the lodge .
- ( horse whinnies ) - FATHER LECTER : Go on !
We 're almost there !
MOTHER LECTER : No , no , no , no . The bath has to be for the dirty ...
- SERVANT : Yes , madame . - FATHER LECTER : In you come .
LOTHAR : Take this .
HANNIBAL : Let 's see if our toys are still there .
- Ah , hand me the bathtub . - I 'll take care of that , sir .
No , no . It 's fine . But let 's hurry .
Cook will have finished packing the kitchen by the time you get back .
Ahh ...
( makes silly sound )
( giggles )
HANNIBAL : Mischa ...
Hannibal , give them here . Mama 's pearls ...
( giggles )
MOTHER LECTER : Ah ... ah ! Woh !
Pearls before swine ...
( chuckles )
HANNIBAL : Mischa ... blow .
Ah !
( motorcycle engine roars )
( jets roar )
( horse whinnies )
( horse grunts )
( horse grunts , neighs loudly )
( footsteps move in quickly )
( men cock guns , rifles )
( horse whinnies , grunts )
( man speaking German )
GRUTAS : Shut up . Shut up !
( soldiers chattering )
You are a Jew . How could I eat your cooking ?
Dispose of him .
( soldiers chattering )
How do you deal with locals , being locals yourself ?
You say you want to be SS . Let 's see you earn it .
Kill the Jew .
Bring me the peasant .
( gasps , groans )
MILKO : Move ! Move !
Move , you fat fucking Jew ! Move ! Move !
( sniffs )
Are you a gypsy ?
- No , sir . - ( laughs )
( sniffing )
( Dortlich laughs )
Are you a Jew ?
- ( gunfire ) - ( horse whinnies )
No , sir .
- GRENTZ : Ha ha , Milko . Good job ! - ( laughing )
Why don 't you show us your dick ? ( laughs )
( all laughing )
- WIRELESS OPERATOR : Major ! - ( beeping )
Russian tanks moving west !
MAJOR : Put all their food on the trucks .
Move it !
- ( explosions in distance ) - ( chattering )
( soldiers chattering )
This forest was full of game .
This war ...
Find us something to eat , Lothar .
Which way home , Hannibal ?
Good boy .
( man speaking in foreign language on radio )
The Germans are falling back from Leningrad .
They are in full retreat .
- Freezing ... and starving . - ( man continues to speak on radio )
( radio shuts off )
( tank roaring through )
- ( giggling ) - What 's that ?
HANNIBAL : Tank ! A Russian tank !
- Get away from the window . - Lothar ! Russians !
Everybody out of the house !
We only want water . The children can stay in the warm .
- Get them inside . - Go on . Look after Mischa .
HANNIBAL : Come here .
Start the pump .
( pump humming )
Wait here .
MISCHA : Mama !
Mama !
Shh !
TANK COMMANDER : How much longer with the pump ?
CREWMAN : A few minutes .
( jets roaring above )
CREWMAN : Stuka !
Stuka ! Shoot ! Shoot !
Get down !
( gunfire , explosions continue )
( groans )
Papa !
HANNIBAL : Papa !
( yelling )
( yells , groans )
( jet roaring )
( screams )
Aah !
( flames roar , loud explosion )
MOTHER LECTER : Mischa !
- Hannibal ! - ( coughs )
- Mama ! - ( gunfire continues )
( pants , gasps for air )
Mama !
Hannibal !
No !
No ! Mischa !
Mischa ! Mischa , go back !
Go back , Mischa !
- Mama ! - No , Mischa , go back !
- ( bullets whizzing ) - Hurry ! Hurry !
Head shots . No holes in the clothes .
( gunshot )
( fires )
( bomb whistles )
( soldier yells )
GRUTAS : Come on , Grentz !
Kolnas , come on !
- GRENTZ : We 're coming ! - KOLNAS : Let 's go !
Hurry !
Put them in the back .
MILKO : Come on ! Run , run , run , run , run !
Start the engine .
I told you , Grutas , we 're going to die !
Relax , we 're getting rich .
- In ! In , in , in ! - Come on , come on !
- Faster , faster ! - Go !
( engine starts )
Grutas , isn 't that the SS Major ?
Major ? Kill a few gypsies , you said .
Kill a few Jews , and they 'll make you SS .
If you had kept your word ,
I would be saying " yes , sir " to you now .
But now ... I am in business for myself .
( gunshot )
He 's not one of ours !
Kill him !
Russians !
Get the body . Hurry !
( groaning )
Don 't kill the dead ones , stupid .
Find the weapons . Find the weapons !
Whoa ! Oh , oh , oh !
Go . Go , go , go . All in .
Come on , come on , come on .
Dump the body ! Dump the body immediately !
( whimpering )
( wolf baying )
- ( rock clangs ) - ( growling )
( radio buzzes )
They 're shooting looters .
Stop and black out .
( distant explosion )
- ( door bangs open ) - Move back !
( growling )
MAN : Don 't shoot !
Come on !
( growling )
Come on .
- Put it down . - Drop it now , you little fuck !
Put it down !
Or we shoot her .
Give me that .
Get the radio , Kolnas .
We 're lucky . Only kids .
If a patrol comes by ...
we saved them ...
and their family 's stuff .
Hey , Dortlich .
Grentz , check the door .
Pot watcher .
Check upstairs .
Find some food .
Hey , only rotten potatoes .
( grunts )
GRUTAS : Find something . Try the- - try the Germans .
Hey , hey , hey , hey , hey .
GRUTAS : Listen , I need information , you idiot .
It 's not a fucking toy .
MILKO : Wait , I have found something under Russian frequency .
GRUTAS : Roadblocks .
Every five kilometers from here to Vilnius .
So , we 're stuck for now , hmm ?
Once we were Lithuanian .
Now we are Russians .
We were Germans before .
Medics .
Police .
And what are we at this moment ?
At this moment , we are starving .
- Unh ! - Did you get something ?
Freezing out there .
Open it .
You think these are peppercorns ?
These are frozen maggots .
This was rotten before it froze !
( grunting )
I 'll put this in your head !
Stop it , Grutas .
( Mischa coughs )
The boy is Hannibal Lecter
and the little girl is Mischa .
( slurping greedily )
( Grutas grunting )
We eat
or die .
( Mischa coughing )
( thunder rumbling )
( boys chanting drill )
( man directing them )
( clanging )
( singing in Russian )
Let 's hear you , little master .
He 's a mute .
He 's not mute at night .
He can scream well enough , and he 'll sing .
This is not your father 's house anymore .
It 's the People 's Orphanage ,
and you 're just one more orphan .
Aah !
HEADMASTER : ( banging ) Lecter ! I 'll see you in my office !
Hannibal , you do not honor the human pecking order .
You 're always hurting the bullies .
I know ,
this was your mother 's room .
Must be difficult for you to live in this house .
Go to bed .
Go to bed !
Everything all right ?
( moans )
( whimpering )
( groans )
- Ah ! - ( growls )
No , please .
( screaming )
Mischa !
( banging )
Get up !
( chains rattling )
Now , scream all you please .
Every day , you 'll pay for this .
Every day for the rest of your short and nasty life .
( water dripping )
( clanging )
( sniffs )
( distant coughing )
( coughs )
Lecter !
He 's not here .
This way .
( screams )
( groans )
( dogs barking )
Okay !
( speaks foreign language )
( whining and barking )
( alarm sounds )
( speaks Russian )
Boy !
( yelling )
( gunfire )
( train whistling )
( dogs barking )
( barks )
( growling )
SERGE : Who 's there ?
Some help you are .
Shoo ! Go !
What is it , Serge ?
A boy , madame .
He has pictures of you and your husband .
Your uncle would have loved to see you , Han .
It has been almost a year since he died .
Only you and I are left now .
( clock chimes )
HANNIBAL : Mischa .
Mischa . Mischa .
Mischa .
( men singing in German )
Mischa ! Mischa !
Hannibal .
- Mischa ! - Hannibal .
Hannibal ! Hannibal ! Wake up !
It 's all right . It 's all right .
When you sleep , do you remember ?
Do you remember what happened to Mischa ?
You look like your uncle , Hannibal .
Would you like to try ?
Use this .
( water boiling )
( gasping ) Hannibal !
Speak to me .
Thank you .
Hannibal .
Here is where I pray to my ancestors
for strength , for courage .
I have the honor only on my ancestor 's birthday
to polish his armor
with oil of cloves .
( inhales )
This is after the fight for Osaka Castle .
The samurai display the heads of their enemies .
There are more suitable parchments that will interest you .
Be gentle , Hannibal .
And be brave .
Like your father .
And like him .
You must be ready for anything .
Come .
Again .
Good .
- Again . - All right .
( people chattering )
Hey , japonaise .
Hey , japonaise !
Monsieur , please .
- Is that all , madame ? - Yes .
Hey , japonaise , tell me the truth .
Does your pussy run crossways ?
With a puff of straight hairs like a little explosion ?
Hannibal !
Don 't move .
( whistles blowing )
The butcher tried to get the knife
while stating he would kill everyone in the market .
Well ...
The butcher ... was Vichy ,
a collaborator with the German occupation .
He 's much hated .
And I can deal with him .
Young man ...
if you 're to be a doctor ,
you must be careful with your hands .
No more fighting ,
and never give more than a single pass .
Forgive me .
I came now to seek revenge .
Hannibal needs peace .
( lyre music playing )
If you 've pissed in my fuel tank , I 'll twist your head off !
- Paul Momund , the butcher . - Ha !
You owe a certain lady an apology .
Apologize to la japonaise ?
Boy , you must be crazy to come here . I 'll throw you in the river .
Or maybe I 'll split your pants
and give you something you don 't want
where you don 't want it .
You inquired about her ... pussy .
You speculated it ran which way ?
Jap pussy runs crossways .
You should fuck that little Jap and see for yourself , huh ?
Crossways like that ?
( gasping )
Aah !
Or more tangential to the spine ?
Ooh .
Do you see how your mouth stains the air ?
I should add that to my drawing .
Would you like to see it ?
Aah ! Aah !
( screaming )
( body hits ground )
Yum .
Wait for me .
You see , it was made with a single blow .
Ah , Inspector Popil . I 'm very happy you could come .
You won 't remember me , but I was with the- -
Of course . You delivered De Rais to Nuremburg
and sat behind him .
I saw you bring the evidence .
It 's an honor , sir .
- What do we have here ? - Paul Momund , or most of him .
You have his dossier .
Yes .
Fat and ugly .
He shipped Jews from Marseille .
He fought recently .
And often .
Last Saturday night , a bar fight . He had many enemies .
A list , please . His recent opponents .
You 've done nothing to this body ?
Oh , no , no , no , monsieur . No , no .
The chief specifically- -
The odor ,
it 's not of anything you use here ?
It smells like that toothache remedy .
Yes , oil of cloves .
Let 's see the pharmacist .
Look .
The most exquisite bits of the fish are the cheeks .
This is true for many creatures .
When carving at the table , you give one cheek to madame ,
the other to the guest of honor .
Did you hear ?
They haven 't found the butcher 's damned ugly head yet .
( distant rustling )
- Good evening , my lady . - ( gasps )
I hope you don 't mind .
I would 've used a butcher 's knife , but the sword seemed so appropriate .
Not a nick in the blade , I promise you .
The butcher was like butter .
You didn 't need to do this for me .
Rudeness is epidemic , my lady .
( horn honks outside )
Police .
They will call it murder .
At worst , a crime of passion .
Wash your hands . Quickly .
Go !
Inspector Pop-il ?
- Popil , madame . - Popil .
Hannibal Lecter ?
Good evening .
You fought with the butcher , Paul Momund , in the market .
Now he is dead .
I must ask you to come along with me .
MAN : Is your name Hannibal Lecter ?
Yes .
Do you have any guilty knowledge of the death of Paul Momund ?
Guilty knowledge ?
Limit your responses to yes or no .
No .
It 's vanilla .
He reacts to nothing .
It 's monstrous .
The butcher had been fishing .
There was blood and scales on his knife , but no fish .
The tape tells you all that ?
Remarkable .
No .
The chef told me you brought a splendid fish in for dinner .
Where did you get that fish ?
By fishing , Inspector .
We keep a baited line in the water behind the boathouse .
I 'll show you if you like .
My specialty is war crimes .
And I know they do not end with the war .
You lost your entire family .
So did I.
And for you , your beautiful aunt came and made up for it all .
The very scent of her must have taken away the smell of the camp .
So when Paul the butcher spewed filth at her ,
I can understand if you killed him .
Tell me what happened , Hannibal .
Together we could show a court there was- -
The very scent of her takes away the smell of the camp .
Do you compose verse , Inspector ?
And keep it under your pillow ?
Now , tell me , Inspector , did you choose war crimes
because you lost family in the war ?
Yes .
How ?
Some in combat , some were shipped east .
Did you catch who did it ?
No .
But they were Vichy , men like the butcher ?
Yes .
Then we are both suspects .
I can say you were fishing with me , if you like .
( knock on door , door opens )
MAN : Inspector , you should see this .
I told you- - keep these people away .
( crowd chattering )
- It 's the butcher ? - Yes , sir .
How long ?
OFFICER : Ten minutes . No longer .
Wait here , please .
Madame , so sorry to disturb you . I was passing with the papers .
Um , your legal residency in France is threatened , madame .
We can delay the death duties
so you can stay in the house for the time being ,
but inevitably , the state will take it and sell it at auction .
You will have to let the staff go .
Good night .
Father , Mother ...
I 'm the youngest student they 've ever admitted into medical school .
It 's a work scholarship .
I think you would be pleased .
Death duties on my uncle 's estate
have finally forced the sale of the chateau .
Lady Murasaki will leave for Paris with me .
This work scholarship means I must spend much of my spare time
preparing bodies for the anatomy class .
My studies are fascinating
and absorb me completely .
Yet I still find myself thinking about my sister
and the men who took her from me .
MISCHA : Let me go !
Do you suppose God intended to eat Isaac ?
That 's why he told Abraham to kill him .
Eat him ?
Of course not .
The Angel intervenes in time .
Not always .
I have to know about Mischa .
I can see their faces in my dreams ,
but I can 't remember what they called each other with their bloody mouths .
I would give anything to remember .
Hannibal ...
Memory is a knife . It can hurt you .
I want to stay here with you .
No . You must stay at school .
POPIL : Louis , I need you to remember .
Who told the Nazis where the children were hidden ?
You must remember .
I can 't bear to think about it .
This will help you remember .
Hannibal Lecter .
What are you doing here ?
The body .
I 'm a medical student now .
Yes , I know . I have followed your progress .
You repeat nothing you hear in this room .
( Louis coughing )
POPIL : Please , Louis ...
Klaus Barbie shipped the children to Auschwitz .
Who told him where the children were hidden ?
Did you tell him ?
When they broke my fingers , I gave them Pardou .
Pardou knew where the children were hidden .
He 's mayor of Belleville now .
( laughs )
Thank you , Louis .
Inspector .
Yes ?
Where were the police ?
( spits )
( priest praying in Latin )
LOUIS : No , no , no . Please , please .
( priest continues praying )
You knew at once what Louis wanted , didn 't you ?
His crucifix to remain with his brain , not his heart .
He answered your question , but you didn 't answer his .
Where were the police when the Nazis threw the children into the trucks ?
( praying )
( soft piano music playing )
( thunder crashes )
MISCHA : Hannibal !
( woman singing in German )
Come and play .
One little cheek .
Two little cheeks .
Cough .
( coughs )
She has pneumonia .
Let 's take her .
She 's going to die anyway .
( singing in German )
( singing )
Hannibal !
( bomb whistling )
( scream )
Come on !
- Get out ! - Grutas. wait !
The dog tags .
GRUTAS : Come on !
- Pot watcher ! Hurry ! - ( bomb whistling )
( men shouting indistinctly )
( train whistle blowing )
( speaking Russian )
Passport .
- Student ? - Yes .
You need a new photograph .
( shouting in foreign language )
Da .
( man singing in foreign language )
Night report .
Entry visas for Kaunas .
Lecter .
The lodge .
( squealing )
" Kolnas . "
" Grutas . "
Mischa .
( spades earth )
Herr Dortlich ...
On behalf of myself and my late family ,
I thank you for coming .
Do you remember the bathtub bubbling on the stove ?
She was dead anyway , I swear she was .
So much mayonnaise , Herr Dortlich .
( Dortlich whimpers )
Where are the others ?
I-I don 't know .
( whistling )
Yes , I know where one of them is , Grentz . I know Grentz .
Grentz ?
In Canada . He got out on the refugee boat from Bremerhaven .
What did he look like ?
Swarthy .
They wouldn 't have let him in the SS !
Oh , yes , of course .
He 's the one that always provided the bowl .
What about Milko ?
All dead , all dead .
In the war .
I remember his singing .
( singing in German )
And now , your leader Grutas .
I don 't know , I don 't know , I don 't know , please !
Please let me go , and I will testify against Grentz .
( continues whistling )
Do you remember " Das Männlein im Walde , " Herr Dortlich ?
# Ein Männlein steht im Walde , ganz still und stumm #
Mischa loved that song .
Let 's sing for Mischa .
# Ein Männlein steht in Walde , ganz still und stumm #
# Es hat von lauter Purpur ein Mäntlein um #
( rope cracks )
You 're not singing .
Sing for slack , Herr Dortlich .
Sag ...
# Sag , wer mag das Männlein sein ... #
# Das da steht im ... #
Uh !
# Das da steht im Walde ... #
( chokes )
It 's Kolnas ! Kolnas deals with him !
# Mit dem purpurroten Mäntelein #
Deals with him .
And where is Kolnas ?
( gurgling )
Fontainebleau .
# Sagt , wer mag das Männlein sein #
- # Das da steht in Wald allein # - ( screaming )
# Mit dem purpurroten Mäntelein #
- ( whistles ) - ( continues screaming )
( chokes )
( head thumps )
Purpurroten Mäntelein , indeed .
( dogs barking )
( men calling )
Picked some wild mushrooms and made a brochette .
Mushrooms and cheeks .
( keys jangling )
( unlocks door )
Where have you been ?
You smell of smoke and blood .
Where did you go ?
I found them .
The men who killed Mischa .
I have the names .
They 're here in France .
Where ?
Fontainebleau .
Ortolans .
He nets them on their way to Africa and serves them for lunch .
They 're like us- - they smell the others cooking ,
and still they try to sing .
Kolnas is using the name of " Kleber . "
It 's on the license .
Monsieur Kleber , residing Rue Juliana .
Morning , how are you ?
Oh , look .
Here he is .
Come by on his way to church to check the till .
How neat he is , and plump , this
war criminal .
( Hannibal whistles " Das Männlein im Walde " )
# Ein Männlein steht in Walde #
# Ganz still und stumm #
Do you know that song ?
# Es hat von lauter Purpur ein Mäntlein um #
Where 's Natalya ?
Huh ? Where is she ?
She 's always wandering off .
Come , come . Come !
We need to go to church .
Hannibal , he has children .
She 's wearing Mischa 's bracelet .
Choose your offering for the church .
Good . Put it in your pocket , hmm ?
Ah , the shiny one .
We 'll put it safe in ...
MRS. KOLNAS : What is it ?
( girl sobs )
( faint yelling )
- Evening . - They 're waiting for you down below .
I called my Soviet friends .
Dortlich 's dog tag was in his mouth .
That means that he has all of our dog tags
- and the pot watcher 's inventory . - MILKO : No , no .
Dortlich searched those ruins before , mm ?
Grutas told him to do it .
Poked around with his picnic fork , the lazy bastard .
Who is he ?
Who is he , this , uh , poisoned little boy
who killed Dortlich , hmm ?
He 's a Paris schoolboy .
They say that there is a passport photograph ,
but they don 't have it yet .
What 's his name ?
Hannibal Lector .
You know him ?
So do you .
We , uh ... we had dinner with him during the war .
( laughing )
Go back to your restaurant , Kolnas .
Hey !
Bring me a covered dish next time .
Where the hell is Dieter ?
Dieter !
You bruise their face , you split their lip , the money goes down .
Come here .
And that one- -
that one is mine , for now .
( laughing ) I didn 't do it !
Milko , I want you to go to Paris .
Kolnas found me a Bösendorfer piano , the best .
Oh , and , uh ...
find the boy .
Lector .
You know what to do with him .
HANNIBAL : Thanks .
( buzzer )
Inspector Popil .
Please come in .
This is , uh , not a social call .
- Where is he ? - I don 't know .
At medical school , I think .
Did you ever see this man ?
No .
His name 's Dortlich .
He 's a war criminal .
He was found near the castle Hannibal came from .
Dortlich had some ugly friends .
I want to know where they are .
Hannibal may know .
Don 't cut yourself .
I know about you .
I know you lost your family , everything ,
when the bomb fell on Hiroshima .
Yes .
You protect Hannibal because he lost everything , too ?
That is your bond with him ?
Do you see your family in your dreams , Inspector ?
Yes .
So do I.
So does he .
If your pet snake strikes in France ,
I will have to seize him , and he will die under the guillotine .
( locking door )
( saw whirring )
( grunting )
Sorry .
( screaming )
( coughing )
It was Grutas who sent you to kill me .
No , not to kill .
To give you money .
Let me give it to you .
No !
( engine running )
( unlocks door )
- You killed so many , Milko . - No !
Many more than these .
Do you feel them in the tank around you ?
Hmm ?
We ate
we ate 12 .
Grutas was very quick .
She felt nothing !
( screaming )
So , Grutas has a house .
Where ?
I have difficulty hearing you .
He has a house ...
( panting )
No !
All right , all right .
Milly-la-Foret .
No , no , no !
Uh , uh , she felt nothing .
( gurgling )
Uh , uh !
No , please !
No !
Oh , Inspector Popil .
What a surprise .
Found in your room .
If you kill in France ...
I will see your head in a bucket .
Do you mind if I work while we talk ?
You killed Dortlich in the woods where your family died .
His face had been eaten .
I would suspect the ravens .
Ravens who made a shish kebab ?
Cannibalism .
It happened on the eastern front .
But you know that , don 't you ? You were there .
This is not the face of your subject .
This is the face of Vladis Grutas , like the pictures in your room .
Did you kill him , too ?
No , I didn 't .
Have you found him ?
If I found him , I give you my word I would bring him to your attention .
Don 't fool with me .
Did you know he sawed off the head of the rabbi at Kaunas ?
He shot gypsy children in the woods .
He walked free at Nuremberg
because a witness got acid poured down her throat .
I 'll need your deposition .
Come with me .
Let 's begin .
Put it down
or I 'll shoot her .
HANNIBAL : Grutas has the eyes of an arctic wolf .
He knew at once to threaten Mischa to make me put down the spear .
At first ...
they needed us for cover in case troops found them .
Later ...
they crowded around ...
feeling our cheeks and arms .
( men singing in German )
( screams )
( screaming )
Hold her head still . Hold her head still !
Mischa !
Hold it still .
Not in here , boss . Not in here .
- ( Mischa cries ) - ( door slams open )
( Mischa crying )
( spits )
Hannibal !
( Mischa screams )
( sighs )
I promised Mischa .
Promised to make them pay a pound of flesh ?
To pay skin for skin ?
If they had killed you ...
who would punish them then ?
The answer is " me . " I will .
( rattling )
If you swear to share what you know with me ...
then I will let you go .
I swear .
- ( presses intercom button ) - Jacques ...
He knows something .
He 'll lead us to Grutas , then we 'll arrest him .
The court has to declare him insane .
Then in the asylum , the doctors can study him and find out what he is .
POPIL : The little-boy-Hannibal died in 1944 out in that snow .
His heart died with Mischa .
What he is now ...
there 's no word for it
except " monster . "
( sniffs )
- ( door opens and closes ) - ( footsteps approaching )
( sighs )
Give these men to the police .
It 's Kolnas 's children , isn 't it ?
No .
( breathing heavily )
Promise me .
MISCHA : Hannibal !
I can 't .
I can 't . I already promised Mischa .
( Murasaki pants )
( door opens and closes )
( footsteps , people chattering )
( clock ticks )
( clock ticking )
( fire crackling )
( explosion )
( car passing by )
( distant chattering )
( car drives on )
( chattering )
( engine stops )
Get out .
( owls hooting )
Give us your identification .
( sniffs )
Where is Milko ?
I don 't know , and I don 't give a damn .
You paid me to bring you this piano .
Get my bike down .
( owl hoots )
( Murasaki sighs )
( inhales )
( gasps )
Shh ...
Don 't worry . I won 't hit you again .
( whimpers )
I like you now .
( whimpering )
- ( Grutas grunts ) - ( woman gasps )
Maybe I fix your teeth .
I want steam .
Turn it up .
- ( cocks gun ) - ( gunfire )
I 'm glad you 're here .
I always felt I owed you something .
( jingles )
( inhales quickly )
I thought you would be bigger .
I put your face on every bully I ever hurt .
- ( grunts ) - ( glass shatters )
Kill him .
( groans )
( groaning )
( flicks lighter open )
( groaning , grunting )
( groans )
Answer me this- -
Would you have fed me to your little sister because you loved her ?
Yes .
There .
There you have it .
Love !
I love myself that much , and I will never apologize to you .
( thud )
GRUTAS : Cut him .
Wait ! Look at me .
And it won 't hurt so much .
( Grutas groans )
( yelling )
- ( woman grunts ) - Bitch !
- ( woman grunting ) - ( gunfire )
( woman screams )
( panting )
Get him ! Go !
- Call Kolnas . - Okay .
( phone rings )
( phone ringing )
To continue our conversation ...
Do you wish to see ... Lady Murasaki ... alive ?
( crunches )
Yes .
( crunching )
- ( grunts ) - ( birds chirp )
( Murasaki grunts )
Listen to her .
Speak to your little fuck boy .
( breathing heavily )
Listen ...
Listen carefully ...
( birds chirping )
GRUTAS : I offer you a life for a life .
Bring me everything you have- -
the dog tags , pot watcher 's little inventory , every fucking thing !
- Where ? - Kilometer 36 on the way to Trilbardou .
There is a telephone kiosk .
Be there at sunrise and wait for a call .
If you are not there , I will send her cheeks ... in the mail !
A life for a life .
- ( hangs up receiver ) - ( dial tone )
( birds chirping )
( breathes in )
I know your asshole ... will look just like a violet .
( crunches )
( crunching )
- ( Grutas moans ) - ( Murasaki grunts )
Take her away .
Kolnas , bring me a jar . ( sniffs )
Kill him at the telephone kiosk .
Bring his balls to the boat .
CAPTAIN : Ready to sail , sir .
- ( Murasaki grunting ) - GRUTAS : Come on !
( Murasaki pants )
I 'm sorry . Your , uh , room isn 't quite ready yet .
I 'll contact room service .
Please ...
Eva !
Clean up the treatment room . Our old guests are leaving .
( speaking foreign language )
GRUTAS : We have a new one checking in .
( banging loudly )
Get out .
See that Dieter cleans them up good before Achmed sees them .
Don 't bite the women . Bite Achmed 's gold .
Drive straight through to Marseille .
( horns blare )
You know what will happen
if you don 't give me some , please .
( sniffs )
( birds chirping quietly )
( Hannibal whistles )
Good evening , Herr Kolnas .
You drink better wine than you serve .
I 'm calling the police .
HANNIBAL : May I get them for you ?
What did I do to you ?
Aside from eating my sister , nothing .
Are you wearing your dog tag , Herr Kolnas ?
Many people look like me . Are you sure you have the right person ?
I was slave labor for the Nazis in the war .
I lost family , too . I understand .
HANNIBAL : Well , to improve your understanding ,
I went by your home on the Rue Juliana .
I went into the children 's room ...
with the sleeping child .
And ... I picked up something for your oven .
( whimpering )
It 's a beef roast , Kolnas .
Do you see how it feels ?
( grunts )
( screams and sizzling )
Lunatic !
( screams )
Where is my daughter ?
What did you do to her ?
Your daughter is safe , Herr Kolnas .
I 'll give her back to you when you give me Lady Murasaki .
If I do that , then I am a dead man .
No .
Grutas will be arrested .
I won 't remember your face .
Help me
or I 'll leave the child to starve .
Where is Lady Murasaki ?
Grutas has a houseboat .
A canal boat . He moves around .
Where 's the boat ?
In the Canal l 'Ourcq , west of Meux .
Where is my child ?
Hello .
ASTRID : Hello .
- Hello , Astrid ? - Yes .
Look at the children .
- Why ? - Just do it !
( door opens )
The children are fine .
They 're sleeping .
Petras ?
Hello ? Petras ?
You tricked me .
No .
I kept my word .
I spare your life for the sake of your children .
( gasps )
( gurgling )
( crunching )
Your boyfriend
ate Dortlich 's face .
( ship horn blows )
Jean , tie her up . I 'll go astern .
( screams )
Help !
Grab it !
- Grab it ! - ( shouting )
Hold it !
( screaming )
( muffled scream )
No !
Hannibal !
Shot in the spine , my little Männlein .
Can 't feel your legs ?
Too bad .
You won 't feel it when I cut off your balls .
A present for you .
A velvet bag .
Can you see ?
Good .
Look at this .
I can put some color in her cheeks .
- ( moans ) - ( grunts )
( gasps )
( straining )
( screams )
Where is Grentz ?
If I tell you
will you kill me quickly ?
Yes .
A village in Canada .
Near Saskatoon .
( groaning )
Stop , Hannibal .
Give him to Popil .
He ate my sister .
( laughs )
So did you .
You ate her , too ,
so why don 't you kill yourself ?
No .
Pot watcher fed her to you in a broth .
Liar .
You have to ... kill
everyone who knows it , don 't you ?
You ate her
half-conscious .
Your little lips greedy around the spoon .
( screams )
( growling )
( screaming )
( screams )
No ! Hannibal stop !
Stop ! Stop !
( screams )
" M " for Mischa .
( gasps and gurgles )
( strained laughing )
Stop .
Stop now .
Forgive them .
Never .
I love you .
What is left in you to love ?
( screams )
( screaming )
( police radio chatter )
No , none .
Find me the captain .
I came as soon as I heard .
Where is Hannibal ?
Come on .
Hannibal !
- Call the fire brigade ! - Yes , Inspector .
Take some men , get down there .
( dogs barking )
Hannibal .
( bell dings )
GRENTZ : Coming .
( clinking )
( dings bell )
GRENTZ : Yes ?
I came to collect a head .
( whistling " Das Männlein im Walde " )
( clinking )
CHILDREN : # Ein Männlein steht im Walde , ganz still und stumm #
# Es hat aus lauter Purpur ein Mäntlein um #
# Sag , wer mag das Männlein sein #
# Das da steht im Wald allein #
# Mit dem purpurroten Mäntelein #